<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<updates>
    <update version="1.0.1.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>First release with Start, End, and Reset options.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.2.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Settings UI refresh, reset master toggle, paused/ended restart detection. Multi-Contract and Load Removal option (pointer-based).</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.3.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Pixel-based load removal (first load and contract-board load), updated Options tab, all resets use Warn on Reset if Gold when enabled.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.4.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Separated Multi-Contract and Load Time Removal options, improved load-removal pixel warnings and Known Issues text, and fixed multi-contract behavior so it works even when Load Time Removal is disabled.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.5.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Clarified README and behavior notes for Multi-Contract and Load Time Removal, documenting how splits and resets behave across chained contracts.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.6.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Fixed the Load Remover, removed pixel and color detection and replaced with reliable memory detection.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.7.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Fixed infinite timer start bug.</change>
            <change>Added New Split Option: Split on Death Leave - Splits on Leaving the Contract after Dying to the Ghost. (Mainly for Hug%)</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.9.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Added 0.16.1.2 Support.</change>
            <change>Version-aware pointer profiles now preserve 0.16.0.0 and 0.16.1.1 support while automatically selecting the correct build data for 0.16.1.2.</change>
            <change>Added dynamic IL2CPP class lookup fallback so minor controller-pointer updates are less likely to break the autosplitter immediately.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
    <update version="1.0.10.0">
        <files>
            <file path="Components/LiveSplit.PhasmophobiaAutosplitter.dll" status="changed"/>
        </files>
        <changelog>
            <change>Hardened dynamic IL2CPP controller lookup fallback for unknown or shifted builds.</change>
            <change>Kept explicit support for 0.16.0.0, 0.16.1.1, and 0.16.1.2 with version-aware profile selection.</change>
            <change>Aligned autosplitter and contract resolvers on the same fallback path for minor game updates.</change>
        </changelog>
    </update>
</updates>
